https://ulsterlinen.com/privacy/

Home / Privacy PolicyThis notice describes our Privacy Policy. By visiting our site, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
What Personal Information About Customers Do We Gather?
Here are the types of information we gather.
Information You Give Us: We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests and communicating with you.
Automatic Information: We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use “cookies,” and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses our Web site.
What About Cookies?
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser, to provide certain features, and to allow storage of items in your shopping cart between visits.
The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.
Do We Share the Information We Receive?
We share information as described below.
Businesses and Individuals: We work closely with other businesses and individuals, and we may share information about you with those businesses and individuals.
Third-Party Service Providers: We may employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include providing Web site services, fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes.
Business Transfers: As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy stores, subsidiaries, or business units. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the promises made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, the customer consents otherwise).
Our Protection and Protection of Others: We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other agreements; or protect our rights, property, or safety and those of our users, and others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
With Your Consent: Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.
How Secure Is Information About Me?
Your information is protected during transmission by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input.
Only the last four digits of your credit card numbers are revealed when confirming an order. Of course, the entire credit card number is transmitted to the appropriate credit card company during order processing.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
Which Information Can I Access?
We give you access to information about your account and your interactions with us for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information.
What Choices Do I Have?
As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase or to take advantage of certain features.
You can add or update certain information on pages such as those referenced in the “Which Information Can I Access?” section. When you update information, a copy of the prior version may be kept for our records.
The Help portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether.
Terms of Use, Notices, and Revisions
If you choose to visit this Web site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, resolution of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington. Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use will change also. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
Search for:
Search
Product categoriesSwatch Cards (12)Linen By Use (218)Linen by Color (221)Linen by Widths (233)Light Weight Linen (93)Medium Weight Linen (100)Heavy Weight Linen (40)Linen Product Line (170)View Finished Product Lines.For Home Linen Products
click here.
For Apparel Linen Products
click here.
Recent Posts
Linen + lockdown: At home with linen
‘Tis the Season to Travel. Pack like a pro with these tips for Traveling with Linen.
How To Remove Just About Any Stain From Your Linen!
How to Become a Linen Laundering Pro in a Few Simple Steps!
The BEST Tips for How to Iron Your Ulster Linen ProperlyWe are fully operational during the Coronavirus COVID-19 pandemic.
We offer Free Shipping in the Contiguous US
-- Volume discounts applied to cart quantity. Dismiss
